You awake?
You hungry?
Always.
You got it.
Spread to the edges!
Where is that cash from?
Work.
One more-job.
Then I'm done.
You don't
belong
in that world.
You heard me.
I approve.
Of the song?
Of the girl.
So who's Debora?
The girl.
I'm done.
Pizza?
Are we celebrating?
Celebrating you getting
a real job.
What kind of job?
Wouldn't it be good
to bring joy to people
when you drive?
Look...
You only have to
wash your hands once
after counting that.
I know.
And not put
other lives
in danger.
I won't let anything bad
happen to you.
I'm not talking
about me.
I'm not blind!
I don't want
your dirty money!
Will you come back?
I don't know.
Is everything going to be OK?
I promised nothing
would happen to you.
And I failed.
But you're safe now.
I'm not talking about me.
Good
luck.